Fallen leaves again?
It's going to be a lot of trouble cleaning them up tomorrow morning.
She's in a lot of trouble too, isn't she.
Miss Sayaka...
There isn't anything I can do, is there?
Oh, Kobato!
Welcome back!
I'm home!
Did you all go out together?
Yeah. Their school held a bazaar.
A bazaar?
Everyone brings stuff to sell!
Then the school uses the money!
That's it!
What shall I do?
Even the obvious things are always so hard
I just want to grin when I'm happy, sing when I'm in love
They say my dreams will come true someday
but when will someday come? I can't wait!
Count one, two, three and spread my arms
Gather the light to myself
Where is it? Tell me what I can do
Even if I'm hurt so much, even if I run so hard
Even if I collapse crying over and over, I still
believe in my amazing future
... Mysterious Life-form.
A bazaar!
Miss Sayaka, let's have a bazaar!
That way we can sell enough to pay off the loan shark!
Kobato...
If we pay him back, then we won't be evicted!
Accounts
Right? So let's have a bazaar!
Kobato, that's...
If we could pay him off that easily, we already would've.
Fujimoto...
It'd work better at a big school. At a nursery with only a few kids, we'd hardly make anything.
It's pointless.
Sorry I got so excited about it.
I'll go sweep up outside now.
She's so excited that it'll hurt her the most if it fails.
So I know why you wanted to talk her out of it, but that's not the way to say so.
If you're too blunt, she'll just think you're being mean.
I...
I got carried away.
Fujimoto and Miss Sayaka have already given up...
I'm so stupid...
Well, you are stupid...
But that enthusiasm isn't a bad thing.
Ioryogi!
Quit squeezing me!
Kobato.
Miss Sayaka...
Let's have a bazaar!
A bazaar?
It's where you bring things from home that you made or you don't need anymore, and we sell them here.
We get to play shopkeeper!?
I wanna sell yakisoba!
That's a nice idea.
I wrote the details on your notes home.
Be sure to show your families.
Okay!
Let's try our best!
Fujimoto.
Aren't you happy Kobato's cheered up?
Doesn't matter to me.
Bye-bye!
See you tomorrow, Miss Sayaka!
Goodbye.
Bazaar!
Nursery
Bazaar
What's this?
It's a doggie!
How about that one?
A kitty!
Don't you think that's pretty insulting to actual dogs and cats?
He's right, there's no arguing with that.
Good work, you two.
Thank you!
Kobato, did you draw this?
Yes!
It's pretty good.
Really.
That's a cute duck and sheep.
Mind if I go ahead?
You have work?
Yeah.
Don't overwork yourself.
Of course not.
Don't overwork yourself, either.
Fujimoto... Smiling and laughing like that...
Mysterious Life-form
All right, I'm leaving.
He's so childish sometimes...
Fujimoto's really into you, Kobato.
Nursery
Bazaar
Yomogi
Fujimoto's just like him. Neither are very up-front.
"Him"?
Good work today, Kobato.
Let's finish preparing for the bazaar tomorrow.
"Him"?
Did she mean her husband?
That's right, you used to order for your husband's birthday.
Yeah...
I guess.
Who was she talking about not being honest with himself?
Dunno.
It's a mystery.
Not as mysterious as your drawings.
You're terrible!
Thanks, everyone!
What's this?
It's a teru-teru bouzu!
Teru-teru bouzu?
They make it sunny out!
Who brought those?
Naomi, you made them?
My teru-teru bouzu make it sunny when you're going on a trip, or to the pool!
Wow, they're great!
I hope they'll sell...
Of course! I'll make something too.
Let's sell ours next to each other.
All right, let's put price tags on everything you brought.
Here.
Kobato...
All right, write neatly.
What?
If we sell a lot of teru-teru bouzu, can the nursery stay here?
Of course, it'll be fine.
Well...
My mommy's gonna have a baby soon.
Really!?
Congratulations!
So...
Mom's taking time off work now...
When the baby gets a little bigger, she'll go back.
And she already knows she wants to send it to Yomogi!
I'll be the big sister coming by every afternoon!
I'll still see you and Miss Sayaka every day!
I want to see you every day, too!
Let's try our best, everyone!
Yeah!
Wow, it's pretty late.
You work at Yomogi Nursery?
Yes.
That voice... You're the girl I talked to on the phone.
You're-
The loan shark.
I'm shutting down the nursery.
I'm not giving her any longer.
You're the guy...
You working overtime?
No!
I just took a while finishing the posters for the bazaar-
You're a bad person! I didn't say that!
You're a funny one.
I thought so when we talked on the phone, too.
Did you talk to Sayaka?
About how I'm not giving her any longer...
Tell her I came here today, too.
And that as soon as time's up, she's getting shut down.
That's horrible!
I don't care if there's kids around.
If you don't want someone to get hurt, you'd better clear out.
See you later, Kobato.
He's shutting the nursery down...
Is he serious?
That's terrible, not caring if there's kids around.
For someone with such a kind face, that man is scary.
That man? Who?
Fujimoto! You were listening!?
I just overheard. You talk to yourself pretty loud.
I wasn't talking to my-
So, which guy?
He seemed like he was grinning...
And he just called Miss Sayaka by her name...
Okiura!?
You know him?
Did Miss Sayaka meet him?
No...
He talked with me, and then he left.
Don't tell Miss Sayaka he was there.
But-!
Just keep it quiet.
What did you go there for?
I won't let you make Sayaka cry any more.
Never show your face around her, got it!?
That man...
He's named Okiura, huh.
I wonder how he knows Miss Sayaka.
Isn't it obvious!?
Sayaka's married, and they have the same last name.
And he just calls her Sayaka.
Then that's her husband!?
Then why does he want to shut down the nursery?
Don't stick your neck out on this one, kid.
Anyway, isn't there something you have to do?
If you don't fill that bottle, you can't go where you want to.
But I'm worried.
And? What have you been sewing?
A mascot!
I'm making them from the cloth Chitose gave me.
What is it, a penguin?
It's a bunny...
You call those ears!?
Whatever! It doesn't matter if it's a penguin!
I'm gonna try my best to make the bazaar a success!
And you're doing this by mass-producing those unidentified objects!?
You're acting like Fujimoto again! You're horrible!
It's gotten pretty cloudy.
It's okay.
I'm sure it will clear up.
That'd be nice.
Yomogi Nursery Bazaar
Ioryogi?
I'm gonna go get something that's sure to sell.
Thanks!
Let's try our best today!
Okay!
I just know your teru-teru bouzu will make it sunny.
Tasty
Coffee
A
Don't trip, Kobato!
Remember, you're carrying drinks.
I won't!
You know you're gonna.
I will not trip!
You two really do get along well.
Not at all.
At all!
Fujimoto brought these in from work.
Thank you...
I knew you were gonna trip.
Sorry...
Don't be so careless.
I've gotta hurry!
I knew you'd trip, Kobato.
Frankfurters
Yakisoba
No one's coming...
Even though we all put up posters...
It's okay. I know your moms are a little late,
but I'm sure other people will turn up.
Welcome
Teru-teru
Bouzu
A
Really?
I don't think anyone's going to come.
I'm the one who wanted to have a bazaar...
Hello!
Chitose!
We've been looking forward to this since Kobato told us about it.
Right?
Right!
Yeah!
Would you like some yakisoba?
We have iced coffee, too!
And we can make café au lait.
Thanks for coming.
I really was looking forward to it.
Chiho and Chise were too.
But, you know...
When I didn't see any posters up today, I thought it was canceled.
That couldn't-
Don't tell me he did it?
Kobato?
I'm going to go tell everyone the bazaar isn't canceled!
Isn't it a bit late for that?
It's not too late!
Maybe they'll still come!
Even if you do, we don't have enough to-
But I want to get a lot of people here!
After all, everyone worked so hard!
We all worked together!
Kobato...
You did too, Fujimoto!
Kobato's such a good girl.
Yeah.
Fujimoto?
They're calling for me. I'd better go prepare the coffee.
He's not really up-front, but he's a good boy.
Yeah.
A chicken?
An ocean sunfish?
kisoba
Drinks Corner
No one's coming.
Even though the rain stopped...
Even though it's sunny now...
Drinks
Hello!
Is this where the bazaar is?
Yes.
Kobato came and told me all about it.
So I came to take a look.
Oh, it's here?
You're having a bazaar?
I wonder what you're selling?
It looks fun!
Where do we start?
Welcome!
Looks like it's a success.
Domoto...
Kobato told me about it.
Where's Kobato? Isn't she back yet?
One iced coffee, please.
Okay! Mister Kiyokazu, one iced coffee!
Here.
This energetic girl walked by yelling about a bazaar at Yomogi Nursery.
She seemed so enthusiastic.
I said I'd check it out later, but then she grabbed me by the hands and dragged me here.
Thank you!
She really stuck out, huh. It's just like her.
Mommy!
Naomi! Sorry I'm late!
A lot of people are at your bazaar.
Yeah!
It's a good thing the weather cleared up.
There's a bazaar at Yomogi Nursery!
Everyone! Be sure to come by!
Be sure to come by!
People all want to fly
but they're cheated by gravity
everyone can really fly
She must be so unhappy because
she forgot her own shadow somewhere
Then...
If you tell me "thanks", if you say "thanks" and smile
Going back and forth, we'll be happy
You'll be happy, there'll be nothing to worry about
As long as we're together
It's strange, I'm crying even though I'm happy
... Mysterious Life-form, #2.
Next episode